GRANT SMITH grantnsmith@gmail.com | (831) 521-1674

Technology troubleshooting expert in multiple OS platforms and a broad range of hardware.

Extensive experience in teaching, coaching, and training in both technical and non-technical environments.

Enrolled in full-stack Web Development bootcamp at the University of Washington, set to graduate in August 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure

2019 - present Seattle, WA

Systems Administrator

- Provide in person and online support for software and hardware systems in a large enterprise environment.
- Troubleshoot known issues and implement long term solutions including updates, new processes, and user education.
- Experience with Yubikeys, Slack Admin role, conference room A/V troubleshooting, Atlassian tools (Confluence, Jira, Bitbucket), Cisco AnyConnect, VPN, Zoom, PagerDuty, and McAfee AV.

Adventure Protocol 2017 - 2019

Co-founder and Content Manager

Santa Cruz, CA

- Developed website from the ground up while managing content contributors and monetizing website through affiliate marketing.
- Self-taught SEO and Wordpress development skills to create a site with 7,000+ views per month.
- Wrote and created content, 100,000+ words in one year.

Santa Catalina School

2014 - 2016

Technology Support Coordinator

Monterey, CA

- Managed installation, user education, and troubleshooting of desktops, printers, copiers, network equipment, projectors, and peripherals.
- Supported systems included Windows XP 10, Mac OSX, TCP/IP systems, MS Office Suite, iOS, Cisco Meraki, Acronis True Image, Parallels, Faronics software, Google Apps. for Education, Google Admin, Spiceworks, Active Directory, and inSSIDer.

Apple Inc. 2012 - 2014
Genius Seattle, WA

- Used troubleshooting skills to quickly resolve client technical issues and educated customers on products while maintaining composure in a fast-paced environment.
- Performed hardware and software repairs on iPhone, iPad, and Mac computers.

CERTIFICATIONS

Apple Certified Mac Technician

2013

Mac Service Certification Exam and OS X Troubleshooting Exam

Apple Certified Mobile Device Technician

2012

iPhone, iPad, iPod Repair and Troubleshooting

EDUCATION

University of Washington

2020

Full-stack web development bootcamp (currently enrolled)

Seattle, WA

Azusa Pacific University

2010

Bachelor of Arts with Honors in Social Science

Azusa, CA